development: &common_settings
  api_key: PASTE_YOUR_TEXTCAPCHA_API_KEY_HERE  # grab one from http://textcaptcha.com/api
  bcrypt_salt: RAKE_GENERATED_SALT_PLACEHOLDER   # must be a valid bcrypt salt, we've generated this one for you randomly
                                               # generate another with; require 'bcrypt'; BCrypt::Engine.generate_salt
  bcrypt_cost: 10 # optional (default is 10) must be > 4 (a larger number means slower, but better encryption)
                  # see http://bcrypt-ruby.rubyforge.org for more information on bcrypt
  questions:
    en:
      - question: 'Is ice hot or cold?'
        answers: 'cold'
      - question: 'what color is an orange?'
        answers: 'orange'
      - question: 'what is two plus 3?'
        answers: '5,five'
      - question: 'what is 5 times two?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'How many colors in the list, green, brown, foot and blue?'
        answers: '3,three'
      - question: 'what is Georges name?'
        answers: 'george'
      - question: '11 minus 1?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'is boiling water hot or cold?'
        answers: 'hot'
      - question: 'what color is my blue shirt today?'
        answers: 'blue'
      - question: 'what is 16 plus 4?'
        answers: '20,twenty'
    es:
      - question: 'Es frio o caliente?'
        answers: 'Frio'
      - question: 'De qu√© color es una naranja?'
        answers: 'Naranja'

test:
  <<: *common_settings
  api_key: 6eh1co0j12mi2ogcoggkkok4o          # for gem test purposes only
  bcrypt_salt: $2a$10$qhSefD6gKtmq6M0AzXk4CO  # for gem test purposes only
  bcrypt_cost: 1

production:
  <<: *common_settings
